bestdegree.net 2008-05-13

# Best Degree

| 

| eLeadsNow Privacy Policy  
---  
We value the trust you place in eLeadsNow. We want to ensure that you understand what information we gather about you, how we use it, and the safeguards we have in place in order to protect it. If you have additional questions or would like further information on this topic, please feel free to write to our customer support department at [support@eLeadsNow.com](file:///E:/office/bestdegree/old/support@eLeadsNow.com). eLeadsNow may update this policy from time to time in its sole discretion. As such, our users are advised to periodically check our privacy policy for changes. We will attempt to post any changes on our website in advance of implementation unless business circumstances dictate otherwise.   
_How does eLeadsNow ensure that your information is secure?_  
eLeadsNow will maintain practices and procedures designed to ensure the security, integrity and confidentiality of customer information. We restrict and limit access to customer information only to those employees who need it to carry out their business functions, and educate our employees about safeguarding customer information and preventing its unauthorized access, disclosure, or use. When credit card information or other personal information is transmitted online, eLeadsNow uses industry standard security measures called SSL (secure socket layer encryption) to encrypt the transmission of data. eLeadsNow will monitor and adopt, as appropriate, new technological improvements that are designed to aid in ensuring the accuracy and security of customer information.  
_What type of information does eLeadsNow collect?_  
eLeadsNow gathers customer information needed to provide superior service, communicate offers on merchandise and services which we believe will be of interest to you, and to administer our business. In order to best serve you, we may gather information from you in several ways, including: 

  * When you visit our website at [http://eLeadsNow.com/](http://eleadsnow.com/), we may collect non-personally identifiable information from you. Through the use of computer "cookies" we collect data, such as your IP address, browser type, domain name, and specific Site web pages through which you click or view. This data is collected automatically and utilized in aggregate to help us look for trends so that we can improve our website and your eLeadsNow experience. Additional information regarding computer cookies and how to disable them is described below. 
  * We may ask you to voluntarily provide information in a few circumstances. When you purchase goods or services from eLeadsNow, we will ask you to voluntarily provide certain personally identifiable information, such as, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card number. We need this information to process and fulfill your order and notify you of order status. Other examples of when we may ask you to voluntarily provide personally identifiable information include if you subscribe to our email program (information such as your name and e-mail address), choose to provide us preference information (such as interests, product preferences, and items purchased), or when you enter one of our promotions (information such as name, address and telephone number). 
  * We sometimes use 3rd party advertising companies to serve and track advertisements appearing on the Site. These companies may employ cookies and action tags to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these 3rd parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. 

_What information do we share and with whom?_  
eLeadsNow does not rent or sell customer information to outside marketers. We may share your information (as described above) with affiliated members of eLeadsNow to provide you with products or services that you have requested or to provide you with promotional offers that we believe will be of interest to you. The eLeadsNow affiliates includes only select businesses with which eLeadsNow has a relationship and which have agreed to adhere to our strict standards for providing quality products and services, responding to your needs, and protecting customer information. 

In certain circumstances, eLeadsNow may share your customer information with trusted service providers that need access to your information to provide operational or other support services. To ensure the confidentiality and security of your information, service providers must agree to safeguard your information in strict compliance with our policy. We also may provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law or when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it. In the event of a sale of all or part of one of our businesses, we may share customer information related to that business as part of the transaction.  
  
_Does eLeadsNow use cookies?_  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by the browser on your hard drive. eLeadsNow may store some information on the visitor's computer in the form of a cookie or similar file. The cookies that are configured by us do not contain any personally identifying information, such as your name, or sensitive information, such as your credit card number. The cookies allow us to recognize you when you return to our site and to provide you with a customized experience that we feel will be of value to you. For example, these files allow us to tailor your eLeadsNow experience to reflect your expressed interests and preferences.  
_Can I disable these cookies?_  
   
Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over cookie files on your computer by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying you when such a file is stored. Please take a look at your particular computer browser for instructions on this function. If you do elect to disable the eLeadsNow cookie, please note that you may not be able to take full advantage of a personalized experience at eLeadsNow.  
_How does eLeadsNow handle personally identifiable information collected on children?_  
   
eLeadsNow does not intentionally target or market its Site towards users under the age of eighteen years and does not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information about visitors less than 18 years of age.  
_Can I "opt out" of receiving promotional e-mails from eLeadsNow?_  
   
eLeadsNow may send you e-mails with promotional offers only if you opt-in to receiving such e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive e-mailed special event information, sales notifications or other messages from eLeadsNow, please send an e-mail to [support@eLeadsNow.com](mailto:support@eLeadsNow.com) and put the word "Unsubscribe" in the subject line and the words “please remove this e-mail address” in the message body. Your e-mail address will thereafter be removed from our marketing list within three business days.  
_How Do I Contact eLeadsNow?_  
   
Our preferred method of contact is by e-mail: [support@eLeadsNow.com](file:///E:/office/bestdegree/old/support@eLeadsNow.com). However, eLeadsNow may also be contacted at our mailing address: 

45 Main Street Suite 309 #262   
Brooklyn, NY 11201
